Monica?
모니카?
What time is it?
지금 몇 시지?
9시
Nine.
But it's dark out.
아직 캄캄한데?
That's because you always
sleep till noon, silly.
넌 늘 대낮까지
자니까 그렇지
This is what nine looks like.
9시엔 원래 이래
I guess I'll get washed up then.
그럼 씻어야겠다
Watch that sunrise.
일출을 봐야지
몰래 숨어드는 거
정말 피곤하다
I'm getting tired of always
sneaking around.
나도 마찬가지야
주말에 어디로 뜰까?
Me too. What if we went away
for the weekend? No interruptions.
방해 전혀 안 받고
종일 벗고 지낼 수 있게
We could be naked
the entire time.
All weekend?
That's a whole lot of naked.
주말 내내?
홀랑 벗고 지낸다?
I'll say I have a conference
and you can have a chef thing.
난 회의 핑계를 댈 테니까
자기는... 요리 쪽으로
뉴저지의 요리박람회에
꼭 가보고 싶었는데
I wanted to go to this
culinary fair in Jersey!
Okay.
You know you're not, though.
진짜 가는 건 아냐
- 알았어
- 갈까?
-Let's go.
-Okay. Wait.
잠깐, 조이는 어떡하고
What about Joey?
The One with the Kips
나 주말에 계획이 생겼어
뉴저지 요리박람회에 갈 거야
I'm going to a culinary fair
in Jersey this weekend.
참 이상하다, 챈들러도
거기 회의에 간다는데
How weird! Chandler just said
he's got a conference there.
That's funny. Seems like
Chandler's conference could've been...
그거 웃기네?
그런 회의라면 코네티컷이나
버몬트에서 열릴 수도 있는데
...in Connecticut or Vermont.
난 회의장소를 결정하는
책임자가 아냐
I'm not in charge of where
the conference is held.
가짜 회의로 오해하잖아
진짜 회의라고
Do you want people to think it's fake?
It's a real conference.
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
레이첼 있어?
얘기 좀 하게
-ls Rachel here?
-No, she's out shopping.
- 아니, 쇼핑하러 갔어
- 젠장!
-Damn!
-What's going on?
무슨 일인데?
에밀리를 오라고 했으니까
I told Emily to come.
And I just need to, you know,
talk to Rachel about it.
아무래도 레이첼한테
다 털어놔야겠어
잠깐!
Wait a minute.
그러니까 에밀리가 오면
레이첼을 못 보게 되는 거야?
When Emily comes,
you won't see Rachel anymore?
지금은 아내를 만나는
부분에만 신경 쓰고 싶어
I'm focusing on the
"I get to see my wife" part...
다른 쪽 얘기하면
나 이렇게 돼
...and not on the part
that makes me do this.
So you'll never be
in a room together?
그럼 둘이 같은 방에
있지도 못하는 거야?
How will that even work?
그게 가능할까?
난들 알 수 있나
I have no idea.
I mean....
But I assure you,
I will figure it out.
하지만 꼭 방법을 찾아낼 거야
It doesn't seem like it'll work.
역시 안 될 것 같다
Hi, guys.
- 나야
- 그래, 왔구나
What's going on?
뭐하고 있어?
We're flipping Monica's mattress.
모니카 매트리스 뒤집으려고
So I'm thinking, basically,
we pick it up and then we flip it.
일단 들어올린 다음
뒤집도록 하자
내 방법보다 낫겠다
That's better than my way.
Hey guys, would you flip mine too?
저기, 얘들아
내 것도 뒤집어줄래?
Oh, man.
어이구...
Oh, look! A letter from my mom.
봐, 엄마 편지야
So, Rach?
저기, 레이첼...
You know how Emily's coming?
에밀리가 어떻게
오게 된 줄 알지?
그럼, 알지
Oh, yeah. I know.
Can you hear anything?
무슨 소리 들려?
Yeah, somebody just said,
"Can you hear anything?"
방금 누가 이랬어
'무슨 소리 들려?'
여보세요, 조이표 방뎅이
Hey, Joey's ass.
What are you doing?
뭐하고 있어?
Remember when they fought
and broke up...
쟤들 대판 싸우고 깨졌을 때
밤새 여기 갇혀서 쫄쫄 굶었잖아
...and we were stuck here
all night with no food?
로스가 식장에서 사고 칠 때
또 그럴 거 같더라고
When Ross said "Rachel" at the wedding,
I figured it'd happen again.
그래서 준비를 좀 했어
So I hid this in here.
Candy bars, crossword puzzles....
캔디 바, 크로스워드 퍼즐
Mad Libs! Mine!
'매드립스'는 내 거얏!
- 좋아, 방에 있는 사람 아무나
- 챈들러
-Okay, "Name of someone in room."
-Chandler.
좀 진지하게 해봐
Come on, seriously.
What do you got in here?
Magazines, Doritos
뭐야, 잡지에다...
Condoms?
콘돔?
You don't know how long
we'll be in here.
얼마나 오래 있을지 모르잖아
We may have to
repopulate the Earth.
다시 인류를
번식시켜야 한다면?
And condoms are the way to do that?
콘돔으로 그게 잘도 되겠다
Anyway, it all boils down to this.
어쨌든 결론은 이렇게 났어
에밀리랑 마지막으로
통회했을 때...
-The last time I talked to Emily
-Oh, my God! Our dog died!
엄마야, 우리 개가 죽었대
-What?
-Oh, my God! LaPooh, our dog!
뭐?
우리 개 라푸...
LaPooh's still alive?
라푸가 아직 살아있었어?
미안
Sorry.
It says he was hit by
an ice cream truck and dragged for...
아이스크림 트럭에 치인 후
끌려간 거리가...
열아홉 블록이래
...nineteen blocks!
-Oh, my God.
-Sweetie, we heard you crying.
이 일을 어째...
이게 무슨 소리야
제발 울지 마
-Please don't cry.
-It's LaPooh!
라푸...
그래, 지금은 '라푸'겠지만
괜찮아질 거야
I know, it's LaPooh right now
but it'll get better.
꿈만 같군, 천국이야
I can't believe it! We're here!
Chocolates on the pillows!
I love that!
베개 위에 초콜릿까지 있네?
조이랑 한번 살아봐
'롤로'가 사방에 깔려있어
You should live with Joey.
Rolos everywhere.
너무 좋다
방해할 사람도 없으니
This is so great.
No one's gonna bother us.
And we're gonna do it.
마음놓고 할 거야
나 모니카랑 한다!
I'm gonna do it with Monica!
챈들러
Chandler, stop yelling
that you and I are gonna do it!
우리 한다고 소리치지 마!
-I'll be right back.
-Okay.
- 금방 올게
- 알았어
어머나
Oh, yes!
모니카, 빨리 와봐
자동차 추격전이야
Get in here.
There's a high-speed car chase on!
방 바꾸자
We're switching rooms.
Oh, dear God!
They gave us glasses!
맙소사, 유리잔을 뒀군
립스틱 묻은 유리잔이야
The glasses have lipstick on them.
유리잔이 그대로 있는데
뭘 믿을 수 있겠어?
Who knows what else
they didn't change?
유리잔을 안 바꿔놔서
방을 바꾸고 싶어?
You wanna switch rooms
because they didn't switch the glasses?
이런 말하긴 싫지만
카펫에서도 냄새 나
I didn't wanna say anything,
but the carpet smells too.
I want this weekend to be perfect.
We can change rooms, can't we?
정말 소중한 주말이잖아
- 방 바꿔도 되지?
- 그래
바꾸려면 빨리 바꿔
5번 헬기 촬영 중단됐어
Okay, but let's do it now.
Chopper Five just lost its feed!
치워라!
Forget it.
나 좀 봐, 저기...
You know how there was something
I wanted to talk to you about?
아까 내가 하려던 얘기 있지?
맞다
Oh, yeah.
그게...
I'm trying to work
things out with Emily.
난 지금 에밀리랑
화해하려는 중이잖아?
Well, there's this...
그런데 한 가지가...
...one thing.
좋아
Here goes.
말할게
I made a promise that
내가 약속을 했는데...
- 이런!
- 왜?
-What?
-Your nose is bleeding.
- 코피 나잖아
- 못살아
-Oh, God!
-You're bleeding.
- 피가 나
- 뭐야!
Oh, not again. This happened when
my grandfather died.
또 이러네, 할아버지
돌아가실 때도 이러더니
Sorry.
미안해
Gross.
됐어, 미안
뭐가 어떻게 됐다고?
Okay. So I'm sorry.
What did you want to tell me?
Sorry. Sorry.
미안, 미안해
그래, 난...
이제 널 볼 수 없어
I can't see you anymore.
그래, 웃기다
나도 너 안 보여
I know, it's ridiculous.
I can't see you, either. All right.
휴지로 코 좀 막고 올게
I'm just gonna go shove
a bunch of tissues in my nose.
코 막을 때 얘기할래?
Hey, do you wanna tell me while I do that?
됐어
I'm good.
-I think you'll like this room more.
-Okay, great.
이 방은 맘에 드실 겁니다
네, 좋아요
They say he's only got
half a tank left.
기름이 반밖에 안 남았대요
반이라고? 아직도
추격전은 많이 남았어
Half a tank? Still lots
of high-speed chasing to do!
분명 캐나다로 갈 겁니다
-I'll bet he's heading for Canada.
-They always do.
다들 그러지
-We're switching rooms again.
-What? Why?
방 다시 바꿔
뭐? 왜?
This has a garden view.
We paid for an ocean view.
이건 정원이 보이는 방이야
우린 바다 쪽 방값을 냈는데
마지막 남은 바다 쪽 방은
참기 힘드실 텐데요
Our last ocean-view room
was unacceptable to you.
-The carpet smelled.
-Like ocean?
카펫도 냄새 나
바다 냄새?
No, like feet.
아니, 발 냄새
실례할게요
Excuse me. Can I talk to you
over here for just a second?
잠깐 얘기 좀 할까?
- 챈들러?
- 그래
들어봐
These clowns want to take us
for a ride. I won't let them.
이 광대들이 우릴 물 먹이는데
더는 못 참아
We're not a couple of suckers.
우린 머저리가 아냐
I hear you, Mugsy.
알았어, 먹시
All these rooms are fine.
방은 다 괜찮으니까
하나만 골라, 난...
Just pick one so I can watch the
Have a perfect, magical
weekend together with you?
자기와 완벽한 마법의
주말을 보내고 싶어
저런, 가스 트럭을
받을 뻔했군
Oh, man, he almost hit a gas truck.
Do you ever watch Baywatch?
'베이워치' 보세요?
여긴 맘에 들어
-This one I like.
-Nothing. Nothing. It's over. Damn it!
없어, 끝나버렸어
망할, 이건 정규방송프로야
This is regularly scheduled
programming!
-I wanted to see them talk to his neighbors.
-Well, I'm standing right here...
이웃들과 얘기하는 걸
봤어야 하는데
난 여기 있어
나한테 얘기해
-...you could talk to me.
-You didn't know him.
자긴 저 사람 모르잖아
TV 좀 끌까?
Can we turn the TV off?
주말 내내 이렇게
보낼 순 없잖아?
Do we really want to spend
the weekend like this?
미안, 내가 방 바꾸는
즐거움을 방해했나?
Am I getting in the way
of the room-switching fun?
Don't blame me for tonight.
나 때문에 오늘밤을
망친 건 아냐
그럼 짐 끌고 방 열 개를
돌아다닌 벨보이 탓인가?
Who should I blame?
The nice bellman?
몰라, 기름 반 통으로 올버니에서
캐나다까지 가려는 바보는 어때?
Or the idiot who thought
he could drive...
...from Albany to Canada
on half a tank of gas?
Do not speak ill of the dead.
죽은 사람 나쁘게
말하는 거 아냐
We're supposed to be spending
a romantic weekend together.
함께 로맨틱한 주말을
보내기로 했잖아
What's the matter?
너 정말 왜 이래?
텔레비전 좀 보자는 게
그렇게 잘못됐나?
I just want to watch
a little television.
Jeez, relax, Mom.
진정하세요, 엄마
What did you say?
뭐라고?
I said, "Jeez, relax, Mon."
진정해요, 몬...
이제 보니 고속질주를
되게 좋아하는구나
You know what, Chandler?
You like fast getaways? Watch this.
잘 봐
누가 고속질주가 좋댔나?
자동차 추격전이 좋댔지!
I don't like fast getaways,
I like car chases.
-Hey, what's up?
-Hey.
왔어?
전부터 하려던 말이 있는데
지금 꼭 해야겠어
I've been wanting to tell you something
and I just have to get it out.
그래, 뭔데?
Okay. What's up?
그 전에 확실히 해두자
코는 괜찮니?
Okay, before I tell you
I just have to know...
...is your nose okay?
그래
Are all the other family pets in good health?
가문의 애완동물들도
모두 건강하고?
보자, 라푸 죽은 후 데이비가 좀
수척해졌지만 튼튼한 거북이니까
Well, Davey's still pining after LaPooh...
...but, you know, he's a tough little turtle.
You know how you said to do
whatever it takes to fix my marriage?
내 결혼을 위해서
뭐든 해보라고 했지?
Yeah, I told you to give Emily
whatever she wants.
그래, 에밀리가
원하는 게 있다면
And while that was good advice,
you should know that what she wants...
좋은 충고였지만 이건 알아둬
에밀리의 바램은...
그래
...is for me not to see you anymore.
너와 내가 다시는
만나지 않는 거야
That's crazy! You can't do that.
What are you going to tell her?
말도 안 돼
그런 게 어디 있어?
뭐라고 할 건데?
Oh, my God!
세상에...
You've already agreed to this.
벌써 그러겠다고 했구나
It's awful, I know.
끔찍하지, 나도 알아
But I have to do this
if I want my marriage to work.
가슴은 아프지만 결혼을
망치지 않기 위해서야
And I do. I have to make
this marriage work. I have to.
난 절대 이 결혼을
포기할 수 없어
But the good thing is, we can still
see each other until she gets here.
하지만 에밀리가 오기 전까진
만나도 괜찮아
Lucky me! Oh, my God!
That is good news, Ross!
난 참 복도 많지!
세상에, 정말 좋은 소식이네
라푸 죽은 뒤로 최고의 뉴스야
That's the best news I've heard
since LaPooh died!
You have no idea what a nightmare
this has been. This is so hard.
넌 내 고통을 이해 못해
얼마나 힘들었는데
정말이야?
그랬니, 로스?
Oh, yeah, really? Is it, Ross?
-Let me make this easier for you.
-What are you doing?
그럼 내가 편하게 해줄게
뭐해?
-Storming out.
-It's your apartment.
나갈 거야
여긴 네 아파트야
Yeah? Well, that's how mad I am!
그 정도로 화났다고!
빌어먹을 롤로!
Damn Rolos!
- 너 왔냐?
- 그래
You're back!
How was your conference?
회의는 어땠는데?
끔찍하더라, 싸웠어...
직장동료랑 주말 내내
It was terrible. I fought with
my colleagues the entire time.
Are you kidding with this?
이걸로 계속 장난칠래?
주말을 완전히 잡친 거야?
So your weekend was a bust?
아니, 엘리베이터 기다리는
도널드 트럼프를 봤어
No, I got to see Donald Trump
waiting for an elevator.
You know, at the Taj Mahal
he has his own private glass elevator.
이거 아니? 타지마할에는
전용 유리 엘리베이터가 있는데
That's right. Made by Otis Elevators.
오터스 엘리베이터가 제작했지
And they don't usually do glass.
보통 유리는 취급 안 하는데
What kinds of stuff do you know?
넌 제대로 아는 게 뭐냐?
안녕
You're back too.
- 너도 왔네?
- 그래
Could I talk to you for a second?
챈들러, 밖에서 잠깐
얘기 좀 할까?
박람회는 어땠니?
-How was your chef thing?
-lt was awful.
엉망이었어
Some people don't
appreciate good food.
좋은 음식의 가치를
모르는 사람이 있어
처음엔 맛이 좋을지 모르지만
Maybe the food tasted good at first...
결국 토하고 설사하게
만드는 음식이겠지
...but then made everybody vomit
and have diarrhea.
챈들러?
모니카?
How much was the room?
I'll pay my half.
방값 절반은 내가 부담할게
- 좋아, 3백 달러
- 3백 달러?
Fine. $300.
$300?
방 하나에 25달러라고 쳐
Just think of it as $25 per room.
What are you guys woofing about?
이게 무슨 소리야?
Chandler stole a 20 from my purse!
챈들러가 내 돈
20달러를 훔쳤어
안 되지
모니카가 훔친 돈을
돌려 받은 것 뿐이야
I was only stealing it back,
the one that she stole from me.
도둑질에 거짓말까지?
Stealing and now lying.
그렇구나
이제 보니까
You know what?
Now that I think about it...
...I constantly find myself
without 20s, and you...
난 줄곧 20달러 지폐가 없는데
넌 항상 수두룩했어
...always have lots.
You should've seen
the look on her face.
그 표정을 봤어야 하는데
레이첼이 날 미워하는 건
원치 않아, 어떡하면 좋냐
I don't want Rachel to hate me.
I don't know what to do.
- 내가 충고할까?
- 그래, 해줘라
-You want my advice?
-Yes. Please.
-You won't like it.
-That's okay.
- 맘에 안 들 텐데?
- 괜찮아
You got married too fast.
넌 결혼을 너무 빨리 했어
-That's not advice.
-I told you.
- 그건 충고가 아냐
- 내가 뭐랬냐?
I'm going to the bathroom.
화장실 간다
If anyone asked me to give up
any of you, I couldn't do it.
누가 나한테 너희 중 하나를
포기하라면 난 못할 것 같아
Me neither.
- 나도
Maybe I could do it.
난 할지도 몰라
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
I know you guys heard about
me and Ross.
나하고 로스 얘기
모두 들었겠지만
종일 생각하느라 힘들었으니
더 이상 얘기하지 말아 줘
But I've been obsessing about it
and would love not to talk about it.
이것도 같은
얘기인지 모르지만
I don't know if this falls
under that category...
...but Ross is right back there.
로스 저기 있다
-That's not Ross.
-Not that guy.
로스가 아닌데?
저 사람은 아냐
그래도 비슷하다 얘
He does look like him, though.
괜찮아, 화장실 갔으니까
Ross is in the bathroom.
맙소사, 벌써 시작이군
Oh, my God! It's happening.
It's already started. I'm Kip.
난 킵이야
- 레이첼...
- 네가 무슨 킵이야?
Yeah, you're not Kip.
킵이 누군지나 알아?
Do you even know who Kip is?
그게 뭐, 넌 레이첼이야
Who cares? You're Rachel.
킵이 누구냐?
Who's Kip?
My old roommate.
We all hung out together.
내 룸메이트 킵
전에 같이 어울렸잖아
오, 그 불쌍한 자식
Oh, that poor bastard.
You told me the story.
He and Monica dated.
봤어? 너희가 얘기했잖아
킵이 모니카랑 사귀다가
깨진 후로는 같은 방에
있을 수도 없었는데
When they broke up, you all
promised you'd stay his friend.
너흰 킵의 친구로 남겠다고
약속했지만 어떻게 됐지?
And what happened?
He got phased out.
- 차츰 밀려났잖아
- 넌 밀려나지 않아
-You won't be phased out.
-Of course I am.
안 밀려나고 배겨?
로스는 네 오빠고
It won't happen to Ross. He's your
brother, your college roommate.
네 대학 룸메이트야
킵 사건은 실수였어
우리가 잘못한 거지
Kip didn't even have to be Kip.
We handled that all wrong.
오래전 일이잖니
It was a long time ago.
그래, 너랑 내가
합류하기 전이잖아
And it was before you and me were around.
They didn't know what they were doing.
그때 얘들이 뭘 알았겠냐?
Chandler had a mustache,
for crying out loud.
챈들러는 콧수염까지 길렀어
It was just a matter of time.
누군가 밀려나는 건 시간문제야
난 그게 피비일 줄 알았는데
I just assumed Phoebe
would be the one to go.
이거 왜 이래, 사는 데도 멀고
친척도 아니고, 제일 튀잖아
You live far away,
you're not related.
You lift right out.
나 왔다
Hey, Mr. Bing.
헤이, 미스터 빙?
That hotel you stayed at called.
네가 묵었던 호텔에서
전화 왔더라
Someone left an eyelash curler
in your room.
누가 눈썹고데기를 놓고 갔대
Yes, that was mine.
그래, 내 거야
I figured you met
a girl and she left it.
같이 잔 여자가
두고 간 게 아니고?
That would have made more sense.
그게 더 일리 있구나
I don't even feel like
I know you anymore.
이제는 나도 너란
인간을 모르겠다
All right, I'm just going
to ask you this one time.
딱 한 번만 물어보자
뭐라고 해도 믿을게
Whatever you say,
I'll believe you.
Were you or were you not...
탔어, 안 탔어?
게이 유람선 말이야
...on a gay cruise?
피비?
I'm sorry about the whole
"lifting out" thing.
튄다고 한 거 미안해
You gotta come with me.
나랑 같이 가자
-Where?
-Wherever I go.
- 어딜?
- 어디가 됐든
You and me, we'll start a new group.
We're the best ones.
함께 새 조직을 만들자
사실 우리가 최고잖아
Okay, but try to get Joey too.
하지만 조이도 데려가
Phoebe, do you mind if l
speak to Rachel alone?
피비, 레이첼이랑
잠깐 얘기 좀 할게
Sure.
그래
Bye, Ross.
안녕, 로스
Forever.
영원히
- 안녕
- 그래
Why are you here?
Isn't this against the rules?
여긴 웬일이야?
규칙에 어긋날 텐데
I talked to Monica.
모니카랑 얘기했어
Look, I'm the one
who made the choice.
이런 선택을 한 것도 나고
상황을 바꾼 것도 나니까
I'm the one who's making
things change.
So I should be the one to,
you know, step back.
아무래도 내가
물러나는 게 좋겠어
No, no, it's okay. Really.
- 로스...
- 아냐, 괜찮아
정말이야
남들은 추수감사절 때나
자기 여동생을 만나고
Plenty of people just see their
sisters at Thanksgiving...
동창회 나갈 때나
룸메이트를 만나고
...their college roommates
at reunions...
...and Joey at Burger King.
버거킹에서나 조이를 만나지
어때... 이제 좀 나아?
Is that better?
No, it's not better.
낫긴 뭐가 나아
I still don't get to see you.
널 볼 수 없는데
What would you do?
If you were me, what would you do?
그럼 어떡하니
너라면 어쩌겠어?
글쎄
First, I'd have said
the right name at my wedding.
결혼식 때 말이 헛 나오는
실수부터 안 했겠지
I can't believe this.
이런 일이 생기다니
I know.
그러게
I am so sorry.
정말 미안해
I know that too.
알고 있어
Hey, Rach?
저기, 레이첼?
Sorry to interrupt, but Phoebe said
you want to talk to me about a trip?
방해해서 미안하지만
피비가 무슨 여행 얘길 하던데
나야
그래
I just came over to drop off...
뭘 좀 돌려주려고...
빈손이구나
...nothing.
So that weekend kind of sucked.
주말을 망쳤지?
Yeah, it did.
그렇게 됐네
So I guess this is over?
그럼 이게 끝인가?
뭐?
You know, you and me.
I mean, it had to end sometime.
알잖아, 너랑 나
언젠간 끝날 거였잖아
Why exactly?
이유가 뭔데?
Because of the weekend.
We had a fight.
주말에 싸웠잖아
Chandler, that's crazy.
그게 무슨 말이야?
If you always gave up
after a fight...
누구랑 싸울 때마다 관계를
정리하면 어떤 여자가...
...you'd never be with anyone
longer than
그럼... 끝난 게 아냐?
This isn't over?
You are so cute!
너 정말 귀엽다
No, no. It was a fight.
그럴 리가 있나
한 번 다툰 건데
You deal with it and you move on.
It's nothing to freak out about.
그러면서 관계가 발전하는 거야
별일도 아니잖아
Really? Okay, great!
정말? 잘됐다
Welcome to an adult relationship.
이제 성인답게 사귀어보자
We're in a relationship?
우리가 사귀나?
I'm afraid so.
그런 것 같네
좋아
나 왔어
어서 와
I heard you saw Donald Trump
at your convention.
모니카, 컨벤션에 가서
도널드 트럼프를 봤다며?
Saw him waiting for an elevator.
그래, 엘리베이터를
기다리더라
Can I use your eyelash curler?
I lost mine.
레이첼, 눈썹고데기 있니?
내 건 잃어버렸나 봐
그래, 화장실에 가봐
It's in the bathroom.
우리 얘기 좀 할까?
Can I talk to you for a second?
당장 해야 돼
안 돼
Yes.
그렇지
그래
You?
너랑? 그리고 너랑?
And you?
But you cannot tell anyone.
No one knows.
그래, 아무도 모르니까
절대 말하지 마
어떻게, 언제?
But how? When?
-lt happened in London.
-ln London!
- 런던에서 그렇게 됐어
- 런던에서?
We didn't want to make
a big deal out of it.
아무한테도 얘기 안 한 건
소란 피우고 싶지 않아서야
But it is a big deal!
I have to tell someone!
소란 피울 일이네
- 말해야겠다
- 얘가 왜 이래!
You can't.
안 돼
-Please. Now, I know this is hard.
-lt is. It hurts.
부탁이야
물론 힘들겠지만
힘들어, 고통스럽고
알아
We just don't want to deal with
telling everyone.
제발, 사람 한번
살리는 셈치고
Please just promise you won't tell.
말 안 한다고 약속해
알았어
All right.
Man, this is unbelievable!
믿을 수가 없네
멋진 사건이다
I mean, it's great!
But....
하지만...
멋진 사건이지
I know. It's great!
그런 거 보기 싫어
I don't want to see that!
We're so stupid.
우린 바보야
쟤들이 뭐 하는지 알아?
Do you know what's going on in there?
They're trying to take Joey!
조이를 채가려는 거야
테니스에서 가장 인기 있는
피비는 오버핸드 피비다
"The most popular Phoebe in tennis
is called the overhand Phoebe.
승자는 패자의 피비를 치며
이렇게 말한다, '안녕, 피비'
If you win, slap your opponent
on the Phoebe and say, 'Hi, Phoebe!'"
괜찮다, 정말 재미있어
That's cute.
We really all enjoyed it.
그래도 점수는 못 줘
-But it doesn't count.
-For what?
점수라니?
Just count in our heads
as good Mad Libs.
그다지 좋은 작품은 아니니까
-I gotta go.
-Fun's over.
- 난 갈래
- 끝났다
Wait, if we follow the rules...
잠깐, 얘들아
규칙을 따르면 재미도 있고
뭔가 의미도 생기잖아
...it's still fun
and it means something.
I'm going to take off.
- 알았습니다
- 아, 네
Guys, rules are good!
얘들아, 규칙은 좋은 거야
Rules help control the fun.
규칙을 따라야 더 재밌다고